

# **PERSONAL PROFILE**

I'm passionate about creating intuitive experiences for the user, through sleek interfaces and in-depth research. My process focuses heavily on investigating user needs and delivering a product or service that matches or exceeds these needs.

### PERSONAL DETAILS

+353 87-271-3351

hello@maireadmurphy.com

www.maireadmurphy.com

Insta: @maireadmurfy

#### **INTERESTS**

I'm currently playing tennis and tag rugby—but I'll really play any kind of sport depending on my surroundings! I'm a big fan of food...so you'll usually find me heaping some cheese onto a cracker.

#### **SKILLS**

- Sketch, Adobe XD, InVision, Illustrator, InDesign & Photoshop, After Effects
- Creativity
- Teamwork
- Project management
- Communication
- HTML & CSS
- French
- | Microsoft Word and PowerPoint

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Lead UI designer on the MyWelfare account for the last 14 months, delivering 8 projects during this time
- Currently managing Deloitte Digital Dublin's InVision account
- Leading monthly *Design* Sharing sessions within Deloitte Digital
- Highly Commended for the visual communications IDI Graduate Award 2015
- Highly Commended in the YCN Student Advertising Awards 2014

## **EDUCATION**

2.1 GPA (BA Honours) in Design

Visual Communications, Limerick School of Art & Design, LIT, 2015

St. Mary's Secondary School, 2011

## **EMPLOYMENT**

UI/UX Designer, Deloitte Digital, Dublin

August 2017 - Current

UX design | UI design | Information architecture | User testing Wireframing | Project management | Design consultancy

Environmental designer, Vision Branding, Dublin

May 2017 - August 2017

Environmental design | Graphic design | Branding Layout design | Print production

Graphic designer, Skaggs Creative, New York

March 2016 - March 2017

Graphic design | Book design | Website design | Branding
Typographic layout | Project management | Online marketing